Privacy/Conditions of Use
-------------------------

American Steamship Company (ASC) requires all visitors to this web site to comply with certain terms and conditions. Your accessing the web site indicates your acknowledgment, acceptance and agreement to the following terms and conditions. Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using this site.

Conditions of Use
-----------------

Information from this web site regarding services and products of ASC is intended for use only in jurisdictions where and to the extent such information services or products may lawfully be offered for use or for sale. Use of this site is subject to all applicable international, federal, state and local laws and regulations.

All products and services of ASC are subject to the terms of any agreement by which they are normally made commercially available. Information on this web site does not constitute an offer to sell products or services.

Information on this web site may contain errors or technical inaccuracies. ASC reserves the right to make changes and corrections at any time without notice. ASC may also make improvements and changes to the products and services described in this web site at any time without notice. ASC makes no commitment to update any information on the web site. ASC accepts no liability for any inaccuracies or omissions in ASC's web site, and any decisions based on information contained in ASC's web site are the sole responsibility of the visitor.

ASC makes no representations or warranties about the information provided through this web site, or any other web site which you may access through this web site, including any hypertext links or any other items used either directly or indirectly from ASC's web site. ASC has no control over the content on a non-ASC web site you access through this web site. In addition, a link to a non-ASC web site does not mean ASC endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or the use of such web site.

INFORMATION, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES ON THIS WEB SITE, OR OBTAINED FROM A WEB SITE TO WHICH THIS SITE IS HYPERLINKED ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL RAND LOGISTICS, INC. OR ASC, THEIR SUBSIDIARIES OR AFFILIATES OR THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS BE LIABLE IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEB SITE OR ANY OTHER HYPERLINKED WEB SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA EVEN IF ASC IS EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. ASC DOES NOT WARRANT THAT INFORMATION ON THIS WEB SITE IS COMPLETE OR UP TO DATE.

Any visitor to the ASC web site providing information to ASC agrees that such information is non-confidential. ASC shall have the right to reproduce, use, disclose, exhibit, display, transfer, create derivative works and distribute the information without limitation. In addition, ASC shall be free to use the information for any purpose, including, but not limited to, the development of products and services incorporating such information. In no event shall ASC be obligated to compensate any party providing such information.

This web site contains statements which may constitute forward-looking statements made pursuant to the safe harbor provision of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. This information may involve risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from the forward-looking statements. Although ASC believes that the expectations reflected in such forward-looking statements are based on reasonable assumptions, such statements are subject to risks and uncertainties and you are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward looking statements.

By accessing this web site, each visitor agrees to submit to the laws of the State of New York, U.S.A. and applicable federal law, notwithstanding the domicile, residence or physical location of the visitor.

Privacy Policy
--------------

ASC will collect general information (such as browser type, files requested, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve the web site and better meet your needs. This web site may have pages that contain "cookies". "Cookies" are data that may be sent to your Web browser by this web site and stored on your computer. This allows ASC servers to recognize you when you visit the web site in the future. Most Web browsers can be configured not to accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you.

ASC will collect only personal information (such as name, address or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our web site or e-mail correspondence. ASC will provide an explanation for the possible use of personal information before collection. The information you supply will be used to respond to your inquiries, supply you with requested information on products and services or track orders. ASC may use third parties to collect, track and process such information. ASC does not intend to collect personal information from children and is committed to complying with laws and regulations governing internet use by children. If you want personal information submitted to ASC by electronic means removed or modified, please contact us. ASC will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request.

It may be necessary to release your personal information if required by law or judicial or governmental investigations.

ASC reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. ASC will modify this Privacy Policy to reflect such modifications.

Copyright © 2024 American Steamship Company. All Rights Reserved.

### ASC is Committed to

\- its People  
   - the Community  
      - the Environment

#### HOME

(716) 635-0222
